[
  {
    "Id": 1,
    "Name": "Test Quiz N1",
    "UserId": 2,
    "QuestionList": [
      {
        "Id": 1,
        "QueStion": "What is capital of USA?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "Washington",
          "Berlin",
          "Tbilisi",
          "Moscow"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Washington"
      },
      {
        "Id": 2,
        "QueStion": "Who is The CEO of SpaceX",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "E.Musk",
          "B.Ivanishvili",
          "T.Chkonia",
          "D.Trump"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "E.Musk"
      },
      {
        "Id": 3,
        "QueStion": "What Language Are We Coding In Right Now?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "C#",
          "Python",
          "C",
          "C\u002B\u002B"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "C#"
      },
      {
        "Id": 4,
        "QueStion": "Where will society be in 30 years?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "NewPlanet",
          "2054Y",
          "Gone",
          "Same"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "2054Y"
      },
      {
        "Id": 5,
        "QueStion": "What Do you think you scored",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "20",
          "40",
          "60",
          "80"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "80"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Id": 2,
    "Name": "Test Quiz N2",
    "UserId": 1,
    "QuestionList": [
      {
        "Id": 1,
        "QueStion": "What is capital of Georgia?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "Washington",
          "Berlin",
          "Tbilisi",
          "Moscow"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Tbilisi"
      },
      {
        "Id": 2,
        "QueStion": "Who is The President Of The USA",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "E.Musk",
          "B.Ivanishvili",
          "T.Chkonia",
          "D.Trump"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "D.Trump"
      },
      {
        "Id": 3,
        "QueStion": "What Language Are We Coding In Right Now?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "C#",
          "Python",
          "C",
          "C\u002B\u002B"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "C#"
      },
      {
        "Id": 4,
        "QueStion": "Where will society be in 3000 years?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "NewPlanet",
          "2054Y",
          "Gone",
          "Same"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Gone"
      },
      {
        "Id": 5,
        "QueStion": "What Do you think you scored",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "20",
          "40",
          "60",
          "80"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "80"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Id": 3,
    "Name": "Test Quiz N3",
    "UserId": 2,
    "QuestionList": [
      {
        "Id": 1,
        "QueStion": "What is capital of Germany?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "Washington",
          "Berlin",
          "Tbilisi",
          "Moscow"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Berlin"
      },
      {
        "Id": 2,
        "QueStion": "Who is The CEO of CocaCola Georgia",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "E.Musk",
          "B.Ivanishvili",
          "T.Chkonia",
          "D.Trump"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "T.Chkonia"
      },
      {
        "Id": 3,
        "QueStion": "What Language Are We Coding In Right Now?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "C#",
          "Python",
          "C",
          "C\u002B\u002B"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "C#"
      },
      {
        "Id": 4,
        "QueStion": "Where will society be in 30 years?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "NewPlanet",
          "2054Y",
          "Gone",
          "Same"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "2054Y"
      },
      {
        "Id": 5,
        "QueStion": "What Do you think you scored",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "20",
          "40",
          "60",
          "80"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "80"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Id": 4,
    "Name": "Test Quiz N4",
    "UserId": 2,
    "QuestionList": [
      {
        "Id": 1,
        "QueStion": "What is capital of USA?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "Washington",
          "Berlin",
          "Tbilisi",
          "Moscow"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Washington"
      },
      {
        "Id": 2,
        "QueStion": "Who is The CEO of SpaceX",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "E.Musk",
          "B.Ivanishvili",
          "T.Chkonia",
          "D.Trump"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "E.Musk"
      },
      {
        "Id": 3,
        "QueStion": "What Language Are We Coding In Right Now?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "C#",
          "Python",
          "C",
          "C\u002B\u002B"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "C#"
      },
      {
        "Id": 4,
        "QueStion": "Where will society be in 30 years?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "NewPlanet",
          "2054Y",
          "Gone",
          "Same"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "2054Y"
      },
      {
        "Id": 5,
        "QueStion": "What Do you think you scored",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "20",
          "40",
          "60",
          "80"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "80"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Id": 5,
    "Name": "Test Quiz N5",
    "UserId": 2,
    "QuestionList": [
      {
        "Id": 1,
        "QueStion": "What is capital of USA?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "Washington",
          "Berlin",
          "Tbilisi",
          "Moscow"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Washington"
      },
      {
        "Id": 2,
        "QueStion": "Who is The CEO of SpaceX",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "E.Musk",
          "B.Ivanishvili",
          "T.Chkonia",
          "D.Trump"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "E.Musk"
      },
      {
        "Id": 3,
        "QueStion": "What Language Are We Coding In Right Now?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "C#",
          "Python",
          "C",
          "C\u002B\u002B"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "C#"
      },
      {
        "Id": 4,
        "QueStion": "Where will society be in 30 years?",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "NewPlanet",
          "2054Y",
          "Gone",
          "Same"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "2054Y"
      },
      {
        "Id": 5,
        "QueStion": "What Do you think you scored",
        "AnswerOptions": [
          "20",
          "40",
          "60",
          "80"
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "80"
      }
    ]
  }
]